what's up everybody this is Nick at
bobbend.com today we are doing a deep
dive on one of my personal favorite
areas of supplementation meal
replacements real places are very
interesting area of supplementation
because truthfully it can be pretty hard
to get in a meal every single time you
need to eat right like in our Go-Go
world it's actually not totally
unreasonable that you would want to get
your protein carbohydrates fat calories
in a shake form and if it's part of a
well-balanced diet and you're making
sure that you're still getting plenty of
Whole Foods and fruits and vegetables it
actually can be very advisable and
indeed a pretty handy way to lose weight
or gain weight if that's your goal so
today we're going to be talking about a
wide range of different types of meal
replacements we're going to have the
best for weight loss the best to weight
gain even get the best meal placement in
a bar if that's what you're interested
in we're also going to be talking about
the common ingredients you're going to
find in your Replacements and different
things you want to keep in mind if this
is an Avenue you're interested in going
down I think this is a really really
interesting subject so let's Dive In
foreign
medical advice that's a pretty important
disclaimer to get out there if you are
looking to make any dramatic changes or
minor changes to your supplement regimen
nutrition regimen or even exercise
regimen anything to do with your health
make sure you speak to a qualified
medical professional who can speak to
your own individual history medications
preferences and that kind of thing with
that out of the way I'm going to give
you a sneak peek at our number one pick
for the best meal replacement shake
because that's probably why you clicked
on this video the best mural placement
is right here it is cage clean meal what
we like about this is that it's pretty
high in protein but it's not too low in
carbohydrates while it still is low
enough in carbohydrates it can probably
work if you're managing your calories in
that regard so in a three scoop set I've
been getting 42 grams of protein 27
grams of carbohydrates and 7 grams of
fat plus this has a solid two dozen
micronutrients added into it and some
adaptogens as well I'm going to get into
that in a little bit more detail later
on but for now I want to answer probably
the most common question we get about
these supplements which is can I just
replace my meals with meal replacement
shakes is that how this works the way we
like to put it is that a good meal
replacement should not replace every
meal but it can replace any meal there's
oftentimes if you need a quick meal it's
going to end up being like a bagel and
some cream cheese right and it's pretty
indisputable from a micronutrient and
micronutrient perspective that a mineral
place would take can be a better option
so provided that you're getting the
macros and the macros that you're after
yeah you just need to make sure you're
also eating fruits and vegetables and
Whole Foods throughout the day because
there are still plenty of areas of
nutrition that aren't covered by just
vitamins and minerals stuff like
antioxidants and phytonutrients the kind
of stuff that you're going to get in
more uh whole plant-based Foods so we're
talking about cage muscles clean meal
and this has taken home three awards for
us we're really impressed with this
product so the reason why I won the best
overall is that it has just a vast array
of micronutrients and also the
macronutrient balance is pretty
favorable too so as mentioned there are
about two dozen nutrients here that's
vitamins and minerals and in a 360
calorie serving you're getting a selled
40 of the recommended daily intake of
all of these vitamins minerals with the
sole exception of potassium now you're
also going to be getting a good three
grams of fiber for every 27 grams of
carbohydrates and also seven grams of
fat and 42 grams of protein on top of
that there are a lot of natural
ingredients in here including like oat
flour organic quinoa there's coconut oil
there's a fruit and vegetable extract
blend as well so technically there's
actual literal like powdered up broccoli
spinach kale and pumpkin and sweet
potato in this put perhaps an extra dose
of antioxidants as well and as I
mentioned earlier it's nice to have
supplements that have some antioxidants
too so they're finding nutrition outside
of just vitamins and minerals although
that's all most people looking for and
this is going to satisfy those folks as
well so it really is a solid product we
also had this as the best mural
placement for protein because again it
has a really nice balance between being
very high in protein and being suitable
for lower carb and lower fat diets
without being so low in carbohydrate
days that you're not really getting much
energy or much fiber from the product it
really is a very good balance and what's
also interesting about this one is that
in addition to being very high in
protein they use what's called IO way
which is this unusual way of treating
whey protein it uses like an atmospheric
plasma treatment to increase the surface
area of the molecules it's all very
complicated but they have done a bit of
research on it that found this type of
whey protein has a higher
bioavailability which basically means
that more of it absorbs which is funny
because whey protein is already the most
bioavailable protein on Earth but they
put some work into this to make even
more of it absorbs that's a really nice
Extra Touch there and this is also third
party tested for band substances and
that kind of stuff so there's a lot to
be confident with in this product
finally this is also our pick the best
noodle placement for weight loss because
on a per calorie basis like protein per
calorie and carbohydrates per calorie it
is a very favorable balance for someone
who is looking to lose weight and keep
their calories more controlled so it's
an easy way to get a good amount of
protein and macronutrients in a weight
loss plan but also if you're trying to
gain muscle there's plenty of protein
here as well so yeah again a great
balance that makes it a good pick for a
vast array of people next up we might
have said we're talking about mirror
placement shakes a bit this time but
there's also a bar here that we consider
to be a really good option if you need a
meal replacement on the go so what we
like about transparent Labs uncut which
is what we named the best meal
replacement bar is that again it's not
just a protein bar it has plenty of
carbohydrates and fat as well so this
here has a good amount of calories which
again makes it a better mirror placement
than something that is low calorie 290
calories in a bar and you're getting
about depending on the flavor like 16
grams of protein that 15 14 grams of fat
23 grams of carbohydrates and three
grams of fiber so that's a really really
solid balance like there's more protein
than fat usually In These Bars and more
carbs than Protein that's a very normal
way to balance your macronutrients
regardless of what your goal is and also
interestingly the ingredient is all
natural too the majority of calories
here coming from roasted almonds and
honey and then whey protein isolate and
they've done a way to mix these up that
is a good amount of fat it's very very
tasty and they haven't added any
artificial flavors or sweetens to it
very tasty a good macro balance enough
calories to keep you full and give you
energy and nice and portable now before
I go any further I know that I am like
getting a lot of information out there
talking about antioxidants and
macronutrients and everything uh so if
you'd rather take this information at
your own pace do a bit of your own
reading we actually made a written
version of this article that you can
Google right so if you just go to Google
and write in barbin best mural placement
shakes this article will come right up
and then you can you know have a look at
the products in a bit more detail look
at the label and the ingredients look at
some of the research that I've been
studying as well and then you can make
the right decision for you if you want
to give that a Google but for now let's
move on to the next pick on the list all
right next up we have the best mural
placement shake for digestion this is an
interesting sort of subcategory in the
realm of supplements and for that one
we're going with this one right here
Health codes complete meal this is the
chocolate macadamia flavor there's also
got a vanilla flavor now when people ask
what is a good digesting meal
replacement shake or protein powder
usually the first thing they're after is
digestive enzymes speak to doctor but a
lot of the time if you have lactase in
there that's going to help you break
down the lactose make it easier to
digest for folks who normally have a bit
of trouble with it so there is lactase
in here which is good because there's a
lot of whey protein concentrate in it
but in addition to that digestive enzyme
of lactase there are eight other
digestive enzymes in here which is the
most I've seen in any supplement ever
and I know a lot of our supplements than
a lot of these videos I've never seen
nine digestive enzymes before and
there's a range of them like lipase
helps to break down fats more
effectively you've got lipase in here
you have a variety of proteases in here
proteases help you to break down protein
more effectively since amylase which
helps to break down carbohydrates more
effectively and then a bunch more and
they most of them fall into one of those
three categories but I mean there are
three macronutrients and there are
enzymes until you break down all of them
in addition to that there's probiotic
bacteria in here as well and probiotic
bacteria there is plenty of evidence
suggesting that having more of them and
supplemented with probiotics can help to
increase nutrient absorption and reduce
digestive discomfort
lastly there's also inulin in here which
is a Prebiotic fiber and that feeds
probiotic bacteria so prebiotics
probiotics and digestive enzymes this
product has it in Spades and if you're
looking for a better digesting meal
placement Shake that's almost certainly
answering a question that this is going
to hit the bill on top of that this is
actually if you believe it the best keto
meal replacement and the best low carb
meal replacement that's the two separate
things people search for they both
typically overlap right so by keto and
by low carb what we're saying is that
this is very low in carbohydrates and
the split of calories per macronutrient
you're getting about 50 of your calories
from the fats and you're getting a low
amount of calories from the
carbohydrates and there's plenty of
protein here as well so you're getting
27 grams of fat for 27 grams of protein
the carbohydrates are just 13 grams and
getting 9 grams of fiber here so the net
carbohydrates are just four grams per
400 calories which is going to make any
keto or low carb person very very happy
if you're getting over 30 of the
recommended intake of fibers that's
going to help to keep you feeling more
full it's going to make it slow the
digestion it's going to do a little bit
more to blunt blood sugar spikes all
this kind of stuff that folks on the
keto diet in particular but also any low
carb diet that tend to like and it's
also made with fully natural ingredients
or no artificial sweeteners in here the
sweetness comes from Stevia leaf and
monk fruit extract so this is very low
net carbohydrates but very high in fiber
and good amount of fat as well so this
is in addition to being the best
digesting protein shake this is without
a doubt the best protein shake for low
carb dyes and for keto diets as well
it's a really nice macronutrient split
and the fact that it's all natural
should make folks even happier so the
best meal replacement shake for both is
transparent Labs mass gainer in two
screws and a two scoop serving is 750
calories 53 grams of protein 110 grams
of carbohydrates and 14 grams of fat so
this is going to fit in very well to a
bulking diet which typically likes to
keep supplements like this low in fat
the carbohydrates are a one to two ratio
so the macronutrient balance I really
really like it's also all natural which
is pretty cool and also the protein
comes from grass-fed wheat concentrate
which a lot of folks like uh because of
the potential more beneficial fatty acid
composition and also just because you
know the cows are more likely to be
happy if they cross fed right lastly the
six grams of fiber per serving so you're
getting a solid like over 20 of the
recommended intake of fiber and every
750 calorie serving in here and of
course you can also just take half a
serving if you want to be a bit more
conservative or just have this as a
snack rather than a meal placement
powder transparent Labs mascara best
mineral placement powder for blocking
next up we'll talk about the best vegan
meal replacement shake which we're
giving to rutana it's the best vegan
meal replacement stick because it is
fully vegan it's also very high in
protein per calorie as well the product
is like 20 to 25 protein by weight and
most of the protein comes from yellow
peas as well as a oat flour and flaxseed
as well because that flaxseed it has a
really good amount of ala like omega-3
fatty acids so in this meal replacement
shake you are getting plenty of protein
plenty of Omega-3s and there's also
plenty of iron B12 and calcium which can
be a little bit tricky sometimes to get
on a vegan diet without supplementation
sometimes so that's why it's our
favorite meal placement shake for vegans
but in addition to that it's also the
best vitamin Rich immuno placement Shake
overall because it's not just that it's
got the classic B12 calcium iron
Trifecta that a lot of plant-based folks
tend to look for in these supplements it
also has about 20 of the recommended
daily intake of 27 vitamins and minerals
so it's really high in just about
anything that you need including like
chloride and selenium which has
interesting links to testosterone
Productions and all these sorts of stuff
so it's a great macaroni nutrient
balance that just about anyone's going
to be happy with there's plenty of fiber
in there as well naturally because it's
a plant-based product and it has 27
vitamins and minerals most people like
they'll be lucky if they get like 20 or
22 in a product like this this really
kind of maxes out all the vitamins and
minerals that you're able to get here so
it's a really really solid supplement we
would definitely recommend it for
plant-based fork and even if you're not
it's pretty tasty and a good way to get
like a vast array of nutrients no matter
what your diet normally is lastly I want
to talk about the meal placement shake
from 310 they've got a pretty
interesting product here that we've
named as the best of people with
diabetes now make sure you speak to a
certified diabetes educator or your
physician before making changes you're
tired especially if it is in the realm
of diabetes but what we found is that
for extra diabetes they tend to prefer
products that uh I have a really solid
amount of fiber and also their doctors
always recommend that they minimize
cholesterol and saturated fat so that's
what I hear because it is actually
plant-based there's zero percent
cholesterol in this and just one gram of
saturated fat for 15 grams of protein
and 2 grams of net carbs so in just 110
calories you are getting 18 of your
recommended intake of fiber of 5 grams
so what that means is that the extra
fiber in there in addition to the
protein can help to minimize blood sugar
spikes and help the slow digestion which
tends to be a priority for folks with
diabetes in addition to that we name
this is the best protein shake for the
elderly that's because again there's no
cholesterol whatsoever there's plenty of
fiber and there's no very little
saturated fat too and all of these tends
to be priorities in that age group we
would have liked more calcium but there
is 28 of the recommended intake of iron
and on top of that this has a blend of
greens like sort of green superfoods so
you've got beetroot spirulina turmeric
and ginger root and all of these
ingredients they have pretty interesting
links to everything from antioxidant
content to a greater nitric oxide
production like vasodilation which could
potentially lower blood pressure and
turmeric and ginger root are pretty well
known for the anti-inflammatory
properties all this stuff tends to be
priorities as well for folks in the
older age brackets so whether you are a
person with diabetes or you are an
elderly person or just simply looking
forward interesting tasty and
antioxidant Rich meal replacement shake
this is a really good place to start so
that's about does it for our list of the
best meal replacement supplements um one
thing I didn't really touch on here is
the cost of these products this one here
is uh 2 to 250 cents per meal of uh
that's 110 calories on the other hand
when you get a product like this one
here health code this comes out at about
four dollars per meal so there's a
breath of prices I've seen more
expensive meal replacements as well but
generally between two and four dollars
per meal is uh is what you're gonna look
at for a solid meal replacement
generally I would say shoot for between
two and four bucks per serving but keep
uh keep in mind how many calories you're
planning to get in the meal replacement
and also what other properties you're
trying to get from it as well so I hope
in this video I what I don't want is to
be just yelling at you and telling you
exactly what you should be buying rather
I'm trying to empower you the viewer
with the tools to make the right
decisions for yourself based on
whichever needs you have and whichever
category you're looking at be it yeah
vegan digestion weight loss weight gain
and so on so I haven't done that in this
video again if you want to read the
written version of this article you can
just Google it with bobbin best mural
placement shakes and it'll come right up
and uh otherwise uh thanks for sticking
around I'll see in the next video
[Music]